upubuntu.com 2013-05-08

# Privacy Policy

##  **Privacy Policy for www.upubuntu.com**

If you want further information or have questions about our privacy policy, we will be pleasd to hear from you at this email address: upubuntu@gmail.com.

At www.upubuntu.com, we give higher importance to the the privacy of our readers. This privacy policy page describes the various types of personal information at www.upubuntu.com.

###  **Log Files**

As other websites do, www.upubuntu.com uses log files. What we may store in these log files includes  visitor IP address (Internet Protocol), country and city, browser's type, ISP (Internet Service Provider), entry/exit pages, and some other information.

###  **Cookies and Web Beacons**

At www.upubuntu.com, we do use cookies to store information about user visits, this will help us record which web pages the user access.

###  **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.upubuntu.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.upubuntu.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.upubuntu.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.upubuntu.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.upubuntu.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

Wednesday, April 04, 2012
